so
you're back
and you brought vermin with you
no
i... brought a friend
you know
i love you
um
you have a very funny way of showing it
so
where are they...
the ghost eyes
hold on
we aren't finished yet, are we
no i suppose not
after all
you still need to find your old parents
don't you
too bad you won't have this
be clever miss even if you win she'll...
never let you go
[Music]
i already know where you've hidden them
well, produce them
they're behind that door
oh they are, are they?
[Music]
mom, dad
go on open it
they'll be there all right
you're wrong coraline
they aren't there
[Music]
now
you're going to stay here forever
no i'm not
[Music]
you horrible cheating girl